{
  "qna": [
    {
      "question": "Organization Headquarters?",
      "answer": "BMW’s headquarters is located in Munich, Germany"
    },
    {
      "question": "Main Countries of Operation?",
      "answer": "Germany, Brazil, China, India, Mexico, the Netherlands, South Africa, the United Kingdom, and the United States."
    },
    {
      "question": "Revenues, profits/losses in 2020?",
      "answer": "BMW's annual revenue for 2020 was $113.076B, a 3.12% decline from 2019."
    },
    {
      "question": "Organization Products?",
      "answer": "BMW primarily manufactures and sells automobiles and motorcycles."
    },
    {
      "question": "Slogan and mission statement?",
      "answer": "BMW’s slogan which has been in use since the 1960s is “Sheer driving pleasure”, they strive to become the world’s leading provider of premium products and services for individual mobility"
    },
    {
      "question": "<ANSWER SLOT>",
      "answer": "<ANSWER SLOT>"
    },
    {
      "question": "Website rating?",
      "answer": "A bland and non-vibrant colour palette, a minimalistic design with an intuitive navigation philosophy. The website has an appropriate amount of images where necessary."
    },
    {
      "question": "Corporation Ethicality?",
      "answer": "BMW is “characterized by clear responsibility, mutual respect, and trust.”. Additionally, about 30% of BMW vehicles are manufactured using recycled and reused materials. Continued research in sustainability is one of BMW’s focus."
    },
    {
      "question": "Less developed countries?",
      "answer": "BMW operates in several less-developed countries including Bulgaria and Thailand."
    },
    {
      "question": "Employee treatment?",
      "answer": "Some less developed countries are Bulgaria and Thailand. BMW promotes human rights and favourable working conditions in the BMW Group, they have a 12-page Group Code on Human Rights and Working Conditions."
    }
  ]
}
